[
  {
    "id": "T7A01",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which term describes the ability of a receiver to detect the presence of a signal?",
    "answers": [
      "Linearity",
      "Sensitivity",
      "Selectivity",
      "Total Harmonic Distortion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A02",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is a transceiver?",
    "answers": [
      "A device that combines a receiver and transmitter",
      "A device for matching feed line impedance to 50 ohms",
      "A device for automatically sending and decoding Morse code",
      "A device for converting receiver and transmitter frequencies to another band"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A03",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following is used to convert a signal from one frequency to another?",
    "answers": [
      "Phase splitter",
      "Mixer",
      "Inverter",
      "Amplifier"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A04",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which term describes the ability of a receiver to discriminate between multiple signals?",
    "answers": [
      "Discrimination ratio",
      "Sensitivity",
      "Selectivity",
      "Harmonic distortion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A05",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the name of a circuit that generates a signal at a specific frequency?",
    "answers": [
      "Reactance modulator",
      "Phase modulator",
      "Low-pass filter",
      "Oscillator"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A06",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What device converts the RF input and output of a transceiver to another band?",
    "answers": [
      "High-pass filter",
      "Low-pass filter",
      "Transverter",
      "Phase converter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A07",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What is the function of a transceiverâ€™s PTT input?",
    "answers": [
      "Input for a key used to send CW",
      "Switches transceiver from receive to transmit when grounded",
      "Provides a transmit tuning tone when grounded",
      "Input for a preamplifier tuning tone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A08",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following describes combining speech with an RF carrier signal?",
    "answers": [
      "Impedance matching",
      "Oscillation",
      "Modulation",
      "Low-pass filtering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A09",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What is the function of the SSB/CW-FM switch on a VHF power amplifier?",
    "answers": [
      "Change the mode of the transmitted signal",
      "Set the amplifier for proper operation in the selected mode",
      "Change the frequency range of the amplifier to operate in the proper segment of the band",
      "Reduce the received signal noise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A10",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What device increases the transmitted output power from a transceiver?",
    "answers": [
      "A voltage divider",
      "An RF power amplifier",
      "An impedance network",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T7A11",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Where is an RF preamplifier installed?",
    "answers": [
      "Between the antenna and receiver",
      "At the output of the transmitter power amplifier",
      "Between the transmitter and the antenna tuner",
      "At the output of the receiver audio amplifier"
    ]
  }
]